

# **Anna Demisheva**

#### **Skills**

- HTML5 90%
- CSS3 75%
- BOOTSTRAP 65%
- SASS 50%
- JS 35%
- PHOTOSHOP 30%
- CMS 45%
- GIT 40%

# **Courses and diplomas**

- JavaScript 2.0, ItGit
- <u>JavaScript Algorithms and</u>
  <u>Data Structures</u>,
  freeCodeCamp.org
- Responsive Web Design, freeCodeCamp.org
- Практический HTML, ItGit
- Frontend basic, WebCamp

#### **DEMISHEVA ANNA**

Kyiv, Ukraine +38 095 32 21 261

demisheva.anna@gmail.com

telegram: @anna\_demisheva

skype: @stilmella

git: demisheva



My theoretical knowledge and practical experience consists of several years of working as a content manager at AWEB Systems and part-timing as a frontend developer at one US-based financial company. My basic job duties are about creating and fixing web pages, migrating sites to the adaptive layout. While working with those projects I got experience with various CMS (like WordPress, Joomla!, Bitrix, Drupal, Wix, etc.) and also have a basic experience of working with existing Angular project. My passion is to make the page structure clear and fancy from both code and visual parts. I'm constantly looking at the new things in the web standards and tooling updates that help to perform my work faster and better.

## Work experience

#### 2018-NOWADAYS, part-time job

Now I'm doing assistance on an Angular based financial web project. It related to analysis and aggregating the financial data for the mortgage industry.

My duties there are related to improving the multiple pages layout. It basically consists of various tables and modals with a lot of data that needs to be presented clearly and adaptively.

The solution should be looking similar at multiple browsers including IE.

The main technologies are flex boxes, grids, bootstrap, floats, sass, invisionapp, and devtools.

#### 2015-2017 Aweb systems, content-manager

I had a pool of projects with the flow of daily tasks that includes: fixing layout, creating the adaptive layout, adding/fixing content, migrating entire sites from one CMS to

another, creating landings, adding scripts to web pages (like maps, JivoSite, external jquery, etc..), adding complex elements (slider, accordions, tabs).

2012-2014 "Institute of Magnetism of the National Academy of Sciences of Ukraine and the Ministry of Education and Science of Youth and Sports of Ukraine", engineer

# Languages

English: B2 / upper-intermediate

Ukrainian: nativeRussian: native

# Interests

- Knitting
- Sport
- Interior design
- Traveling
- Cooking

### **Education**

2007-2013 National Technical University of Ukraine "Igor Sikorsky Kyiv Polytechnic Institute", Faculty of Chemical Engineering

# **Personality**

- I am constantly engaged in self-improvement, I improve my qualifications at courses and trainings, I am ready for further training
- Conscientious about my work
- I always try to complete tasks on time
- Organized
- Ability to make deliberate, rational decisions